Do not attempt this at home.
Jackass: The Movie is a action, comedy,
documentary film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
Johnny Knoxville and his band of maniacs perform a variety of stunts
and gross-out gags on the big screen for the first time.
They wander around Japan in panda outfits, wreak havoc on a once civilized golf
course, they even do stunts involving LIVE alligators, and so on.
Self, played by Johnny Knoxville.
Self, played by Bam Margera.
Self, played by Steve-O.
Self, played by Chris Pontius.
Self, played by Ryan Dunn.
Self, played by Jason 'Wee Man' Acuña.
Jackass: The Movie is a 2002 American reality slapstick
comedy film directed by Jeff Tremaine.
It is a continuation of the MTV television series
Jackass, which had completed its run.
It was produced by Lynch Siderow Productions and Dickhouse Productions.
The film features most of the original Jackass cast, including leader Johnny Knoxville, Bam Margera, Chris
Pontius, Steve-O, Dave England, Ryan Dunn, Jason "Wee Man" Acuña, Preston Lacy and Ehren McGhehey.
MTV Films and Paramount Pictures released the film
to theaters on October 25, 2002.
It grossed over $79 million worldwide and received mixed reviews from critics.
It was followed by a sequel, Jackass Number Two (2006).
The film explores themes of pain, idiot, disgust, stunt, music video.
The tone is lighthearted.